[{"url":"https://actualnewsmagazine.com/english/2024-us-presidential-election-the-rematch-they-dont-want/","authorsByline":"admin","articleId":"55fae3272a1a4163a576bb367f5be003","clusterId":"2d6ad60cc2874f0e8d0806d4f9824737","source":{"domain":"actualnewsmagazine.com"},"imageUrl":"https://actualnewsmagazine.com/english/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/United-States-Where-the-center-no-longer-exists.jpg","country":"us","language":"en","pubDate":"2024-01-17T02:10:28+00:00","addDate":"2024-01-17T02:27:43.587964+00:00","refreshDate":"2024-01-17T02:27:43.587965+00:00","score":142.5194,"title":"2024 - 2024 US presidential election","description":"Polls indicate that at least half of Americans would not want next November's election to be a rematch between Joe Biden and Donald Trump. They better get","content":"","medium":"Article","links":[],"labels":[{"name":"Low Content"}],"matchedAuthors":[],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[],"topics":[],"categories":[{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[],"companies":[],"summary":"","translation":"","translatedTitle":"","translatedDescription":"","translatedSummary":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"1dfd1216339e4166afc408970f9397bd","places":[],"people":[],"sentiment":{}},{"url":"https://www.scmp.com/topics/us-presidential-election-2024","authorsByline":"","articleId":"8b61d670a4b547f3876ef5765c542e12","clusterId":"2c59e90f0faf464cbd0640010830c6e7","source":{"domain":"scmp.com","paywall":true},"imageUrl":"https://www.scmp.com/static/img/icons/scmp-meta-1200x630.png","country":"us","language":"en","pubDate":"2022-11-22T18:28:26+00:00","addDate":"2022-11-22T18:40:50.697282+00:00","refreshDate":"2022-11-22T18:40:50.697283+00:00","score":142.1256,"title":"US Presidential Election 2024","description":"Latest news, updates, analysis and opinion about the 2024 United States Presidential Election. Donald Trump got a jump on the election cycle in November 2022 when he announced that he would run for president a third time; the competition is expected to heat up further into 2023, as candidates make their pitches to be chosen as the contender for their respective parties.","content":"Latest news, updates, analysis and opinion about the 2024 United States Presidential Election. Donald Trump got a jump on the election cycle in November 2022 when he announced that he would run for pr... [372 symbols]","medium":"Article","links":[],"labels":[],"matchedAuthors":[],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[{"name":"US Presidential Election","weight":0.1409},{"name":"United States","weight":0.1056},{"name":"candidates","weight":0.1029},{"name":"their respective parties","weight":0.0939},{"name":"third","weight":0.0935},{"name":"president","weight":0.0909},{"name":"November","weight":0.0813},{"name":"the 2024 United States Presidential Election","weight":0.0741},{"name":"opinion","weight":0.0724},{"name":"analysis","weight":0.0675}],"topics":[{"name":"2024 Elections"}],"categories":[{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[{"data":"US","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"United States","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Donald Trump","type":"PERSON","mentions":1}],"companies":[],"summary":"US Presidential Election 2024. \n\nLatest news, updates, analysis and opinion about the 2024 United States Presidential Election. Donald Trump got a jump on the election cycle in November 2022 when he announced that he would run for president a third time; the competition is expected to heat up further into 2023, as candidates make their pitches to be chosen as the contender for their respective parties.","translation":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"e3a189c00d204b53b87513b0ab74e482","places":[],"people":[{"wikidataId":"Q22686","name":"Donald Trump"}],"sentiment":{"positive":0.0844,"negative":0.0195,"neutral":0.896}},{"url":"https://newsjani.com/uncategorized/us-presidential-election-2024-usa-nikki-haleys-big-announcement-of-indian-origin-she-will-contest-the-presidential-election-news-jani/","authorsByline":"","articleId":"b46ecfa85f7a4e9c9e9d3117c3144c37","clusterId":"05600ba9f7694a54b70d5e3dc3c3e873","source":{"domain":"newsjani.com"},"imageUrl":"https://s.enavabharat.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Nikki-Haley.jpg","country":"us","language":"en","pubDate":"2023-02-14T14:29:04+00:00","addDate":"2023-02-14T14:46:55.919560+00:00","refreshDate":"2023-02-14T14:46:55.919561+00:00","score":142.1256,"title":"US Presidential Election 2024","description":"US Presidential Election 2024","content":"US Presidential Election 2024 | USA: Nikki Haley’s big announcement of Indian origin, she will contest the presidential election\n\nWashingtonProminent Indian-American leader Nikki Haley launched her ca... [1250 symbols]","medium":"Article","links":[],"labels":[],"matchedAuthors":[],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[{"name":"Trump","weight":0.1278},{"name":"Donald Trump","weight":0.1275},{"name":"former US President Donald Trump","weight":0.1225},{"name":"Indian immigrants","weight":0.0936},{"name":"Indian origin","weight":0.0868},{"name":"Indian","weight":0.0802},{"name":"Nikki Haley","weight":0.0771},{"name":"weeks","weight":0.0744},{"name":"WashingtonProminent Indian-American leader Nikki Haley","weight":0.0732},{"name":"US Presidential Election","weight":0.068}],"topics":[{"name":"2024 Elections"},{"name":"Nikki Haley"}],"categories":[{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[{"data":"US","type":"GPE","mentions":5},{"data":"South Carolina","type":"GPE","mentions":2},{"data":"Bamberg","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"America","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Nikki Haley’s","type":"PERSON","mentions":5},{"data":"Donald Trump","type":"PERSON","mentions":3},{"data":"Indian","type":"NORP","mentions":3},{"data":"Republican","type":"NORP","mentions":1},{"data":"the White House","type":"FAC","mentions":2},{"data":"the United Nations","type":"ORG","mentions":1}],"companies":[],"summary":"Nikki Haley’s big announcement of Indian origin, she will contest the presidential election\n\nWashingtonProminent Indian-American leader Nikki Haley launched her campaign for the presidency on Tuesday. Thus, she has become the first Republican to challenge former US President Donald Trump to become his party’s candidate for the White House in 2024. We must turn in that direction again.”\n\nHaley has been hinting at a run for the White House for weeks, positioning herself as a younger and fresher alternative to Trump. Her official announcement means she will be the first contender to run against her former boss, 76-year-old Trump.","translation":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"811163a21bf343c4952661a4f7b76a0f","places":[],"people":[{"wikidataId":"Q22686","name":"Donald Trump"},{"wikidataId":"Q11668","name":"Nikki Haley"}],"sentiment":{"positive":0.2171,"negative":0.0201,"neutral":0.7628}},{"url":"https://paulstulac.com/us-presidential-election-2024-ron-desantis-says-he-can-beat-biden/","authorsByline":"nchal","articleId":"03ef30374a4f4f1aae656962c500a383","clusterId":"a56373a494b742b5b43466a85778f609","source":{"domain":"paulstulac.com"},"imageUrl":"https://mobile-img.lpcdn.ca/v2/924x/r3996/47c243f3b3663b03937fb3ce137de875.jpg","country":"us","language":"en","pubDate":"2023-03-22T17:37:59+00:00","addDate":"2023-03-22T17:47:55.685045+00:00","refreshDate":"2023-03-22T17:47:55.685046+00:00","score":142.1256,"title":"US Presidential Election 2024","description":"(Miami) Republican Ron DeSantis said he could beat Joe Biden for the 2024 U.S. presidential election, according to an interview the first snippets of which","content":"(Miami) Republican Ron DeSantis said he could beat Joe Biden for the 2024 U.S. presidential election, according to an interview the first snippets of which aired Wednesday.\n\n“I have what it takes to b... [1367 symbols]","medium":"Article","links":[],"labels":[],"matchedAuthors":[{"name":"Nchal"}],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[{"name":"Ron DeSantis","weight":0.0992},{"name":"ultra-conservative blows","weight":0.0801},{"name":"Fox Nation","weight":0.077},{"name":"Joe Biden","weight":0.0736},{"name":"President Joe Biden","weight":0.0729},{"name":"Donald Trump","weight":0.0719},{"name":"immigration","weight":0.0718},{"name":"daily dramas","weight":0.0686},{"name":"Piers Morgan","weight":0.0683},{"name":"US Presidential Election","weight":0.0682}],"topics":[{"name":"Joe Biden"},{"name":"2024 Elections"},{"name":"Ron DeSantis"}],"categories":[{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[{"data":"US","type":"GPE","mentions":3},{"data":"Miami","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Florida","type":"GPE","mentions":2},{"data":"Republican","type":"NORP","mentions":3},{"data":"American","type":"NORP","mentions":1},{"data":"Democratic","type":"NORP","mentions":1},{"data":"Ron DeSantis","type":"PERSON","mentions":3},{"data":"Joe Biden","type":"PERSON","mentions":3},{"data":"Piers Morgan","type":"PERSON","mentions":1},{"data":"Murdoch","type":"PERSON","mentions":1},{"data":"Donald Trump","type":"PERSON","mentions":2},{"data":"evening","type":"TIME","mentions":1},{"data":"TalkTV","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"Fox Nation","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"the New York Post","type":"ORG","mentions":1}],"companies":[],"summary":"Ron DeSantis, the Republican governor of Florida, has said he could beat Joe Biden for the 2024 US Presidential Election 2024. In an interview with journalist and polemicist presenter Piers Morgan, he discussed his potential candidacy and attacked Donald Trump, likely his biggest rival for the nomination. He was recently elected head of the US state of Florida after being endorsed by Donald Trump and has since distanced himself from the excesses of his ideas. On the Democratic side, President Joe Biden has promised to make his decision public at the beginning of the year.","translation":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"5ac16e2905704dcf8395610d700315c6","places":[],"people":[{"wikidataId":"Q22686","name":"Donald Trump"},{"wikidataId":"Q3105215","name":"Ron DeSantis"},{"wikidataId":"Q6279","name":"Joe Biden"}],"sentiment":{"positive":0.0736,"negative":0.1436,"neutral":0.7828}},{"url":"https://abbonews.com/us-presidential-election-2024-us-president-joe-biden-announces-his-re-election-bid-in-2024-abbo-news/","authorsByline":"","articleId":"2e765c6e7e8b49f5b8b3bdbd95f351df","clusterId":"65ec237632fc4e3a86b308877737178a","source":{"domain":"abbonews.com"},"imageUrl":"https://s.enavabharat.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/joe-biden.jpg","country":"us","language":"en","pubDate":"2023-04-25T17:39:00+00:00","addDate":"2023-04-25T17:48:22.338598+00:00","refreshDate":"2023-04-25T17:48:22.338599+00:00","score":142.1256,"title":"US Presidential Election 2024","description":"US Presidential Election 2024","content":"Washington. President Joe Biden on Tuesday announced his bid for the top job again in 2024, less than three years after defeating his predecessor, Donald Trump. He launched his campaign by calling on ... [4835 symbols]","medium":"Article","links":["https://t.co/KPyedMz6pA","https://twitter.com/ANI/status/1650803131796561920?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"],"labels":[],"matchedAuthors":[],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[{"name":"more rights","weight":0.0926},{"name":"more freedom","weight":0.0849},{"name":"abortion rights","weight":0.0837},{"name":"less freedom","weight":0.0832},{"name":"abortion rights activists","weight":0.0815},{"name":"voting rights","weight":0.0806},{"name":"rights","weight":0.0797},{"name":"President Joe Biden","weight":0.0724},{"name":"Joe Biden","weight":0.0702},{"name":"Freedom","weight":0.0694}],"topics":[{"name":"2024 Elections"},{"name":"Joe Biden"}],"categories":[{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[{"data":"US","type":"GPE","mentions":4},{"data":"Washington","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"the United States","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"America","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Afghanistan","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"China","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Iran","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Ukraine","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Joe Biden","type":"PERSON","mentions":15},{"data":"Donald Trump","type":"PERSON","mentions":5},{"data":"Kamala Harris","type":"PERSON","mentions":8},{"data":"Nikki Haley","type":"PERSON","mentions":1},{"data":"Vivek Ramaswamy","type":"PERSON","mentions":1},{"data":"Americans","type":"NORP","mentions":13},{"data":"Republican","type":"NORP","mentions":3},{"data":"the Democratic Party","type":"ORG","mentions":2},{"data":"Social Security","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"the US Supreme Court","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"the Republican Party","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"the White House","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"three-minute","type":"TIME","mentions":1},{"data":"World War III","type":"EVENT","mentions":2}],"companies":[],"summary":"President Joe Biden on Tuesday announced his bid for the top job again in 2024, less than three years after defeating his predecessor, Donald Trump. He launched his campaign by calling on Americans to re-elect him, along with Vice President Kamala Harris, to save democracy and “finish the job.” Vice President Harris urged Americans to come together to fight for democracy, continue progress and ensure that all Americans thrive and prosper. In Biden's announcement, he said that abortion rights, protecting democracy, voting rights and the Social Security system will be among the most important issues in the 2024 election. Former US President Donald Trump is currently leading Republicans to win the party’s nomination to challenge him next November.","translation":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"19846e7fb743494da3dcb7ae7b5c8c9b","places":[],"people":[{"wikidataId":"Q22686","name":"Donald Trump"},{"wikidataId":"Q27881473","name":"Vivek Ramaswamy"},{"wikidataId":"Q10853588","name":"Kamala Harris"},{"wikidataId":"Q11668","name":"Nikki Haley"},{"wikidataId":"Q6279","name":"Joe Biden"}],"sentiment":{"positive":0.0634,"negative":0.0533,"neutral":0.8833}},{"url":"https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/joe-biden-is-currently-the-most-unpopular-us-president-in-modern-history--what-ails-his-presidency-18536391.htm","authorsByline":"Vijay Anand","articleId":"5ee18acb30314381a4c8ccbbf32a9f81","clusterId":"a0011e9c12c3426f936bd64a79a80772","source":{"domain":"cnbctv18.com"},"imageUrl":"https://images.cnbctv18.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2023-10-02t211205z-1594625017-rc2gk3aavhs4-rtrmadp-3-usa-biden-1019x573.jpg","country":"in","language":"en","pubDate":"2023-12-11T11:41:41+00:00","addDate":"2023-12-11T11:59:49.879076+00:00","refreshDate":"2023-12-11T11:59:49.879077+00:00","score":142.1256,"title":"US Presidential Election 2024","description":"US Presidential Election 2024","content":"Joe Biden has completed 1,054 days in office and, going by the latest polling data compiled by FiveThirtyEight (538), the 46th US President has the lowest approval rating of any of his predecessors at... [3827 symbols]","medium":"Article","links":["https://www.cnbctv18.com/tags/ron-desantis.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/gop-republican-debate-donal-trump-nikki-haley-ron-desantis-vivek-ramaswamy-miami-18282031.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/former-us-president-donald-trump-shouts-at-judge-and-lawyers-in-wild-day-on-witness-stand-18258431.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/joe-biden-vs-donald-trump-who-will-win-if-the-us-presidential-election-is-held-today-18421351.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/vivek-ramaswamy-us-presidential-elections-candidate-2024-17587401.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/joe-biden-to-press-congress-to-pass-ukraine-aid-package-18507581.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/politics/this-is-how-global-leaders-reacted-to-joe-bidens-election-win-7428721.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/donald-trump-indictment-78-charges-prison-time-justice-department-former-us-president-17410621.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/us-consumer-confidence-rises-house-prices-accelerate-18427911.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/economy/us-inflation-hits-40-year-high-of-nearly-9-percent-13781792.htm"],"labels":[],"matchedAuthors":[{"id":"1da1f1686906438f85e594d91ae46e72","name":"Vijay Anand"}],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[{"name":"job approval polling","weight":0.0744},{"name":"US inflation","weight":0.0731},{"name":"price increases","weight":0.0659},{"name":"US","weight":0.0642},{"name":"US Presidential Election","weight":0.0637},{"name":"rising prices","weight":0.0628},{"name":"financial stress","weight":0.0617},{"name":"Biden","weight":0.061},{"name":"Joe Biden","weight":0.0597},{"name":"several key points","weight":0.058}],"topics":[{"name":"2024 Elections"},{"name":"Joe Biden"}],"categories":[{"name":"World"},{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[{"data":"US Presidential Election","type":"EVENT","mentions":1},{"data":"Joe Biden","type":"PERSON","mentions":11},{"data":"Harry S. Truman","type":"PERSON","mentions":1},{"data":"Donald Trump","type":"PERSON","mentions":6},{"data":"Ron DeSantis","type":"PERSON","mentions":1},{"data":"FiveThirtyEight","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"FT-Michigan Ross","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"CBS","type":"ORG","mentions":2},{"data":"US","type":"GPE","mentions":7},{"data":"America","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Ukraine","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Israel","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Republican","type":"NORP","mentions":4},{"data":"Americans","type":"NORP","mentions":4},{"data":"Democrats","type":"NORP","mentions":3}],"companies":[],"summary":"Joe Biden, the 46th US President, has received the lowest job approval rating of any predecessor in his first term since Harry S. Truman in 1948. According to FiveThirtyEight (538), Biden currently holds a 37.7% approval rating, the lowest of any of his predecessors. This comes as Donald Trump, Biden's Republican predecessor and likely opponent, is leading in the Republican presidential primaries with 59.3% and a 47-percent lead over second-place Ron DeSantis. A recent survey by FT-Michigan Ross found that only 25% of respondents view the state of the US economy as \"good\" or \"excellent\". High inflation remains a major concern for Americans, and 53% feel worse off financially since Biden took office. Rising consumer costs, particularly price increases, remain a significant financial challenge. Meanwhile, Biden faces discontent within his own party, particularly from young voters, and his approval has been significantly decreased among these voters.","translation":"","translatedTitle":"","translatedDescription":"","translatedSummary":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"9e029e03eb5545fdb2bf8512b57b81f6","places":[],"people":[{"wikidataId":"Q22686","name":"Donald Trump"},{"wikidataId":"Q3105215","name":"Ron DeSantis"},{"wikidataId":"Q6279","name":"Joe Biden"}],"sentiment":{"positive":0.0526,"negative":0.7948,"neutral":0.1525}},{"url":"https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/us-presidential-election-2024--desantis-haley-exchange-barbs-at-debate-as-primary-season-looms-18772451.htm","authorsByline":"Vijay Anand","articleId":"da6984988d3047e0a456d74a4226ccb1","clusterId":"c31ba9b0ecd148da8b4584e7e80e5002","source":{"domain":"cnbctv18.com"},"imageUrl":"https://images.cnbctv18.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/gop-debate-1-1019x573.jpg","country":"in","language":"en","pubDate":"2024-01-11T10:23:46+00:00","addDate":"2024-01-11T10:41:13.645817+00:00","refreshDate":"2024-01-11T10:41:13.645819+00:00","score":142.1256,"title":"US Presidential Election 2024","description":"US presidential candidates Nikki Haley and Ron DeSantis clashed in the Iowa debate ahead of the Republican primaries, accusing each other of lies and resorting to character attacks. They diverged on immigration, foreign policy, and leadership styles. Despite a focus on mutual criticism, no clear winner emerged from the debate, with former US President Donald Trump still way ahead in polls, despite his numerous legal troubles.","content":"With days to go before the Republican presidential primaries for the US Presidential Election kick off — the Iowa caucuses will be held on Monday — GOP hopefuls Nikki Haley and Florida Governor Ron De... [3771 symbols]","medium":"Article","links":["https://twitter.com/NikkiHaley/status/1745288758209986878?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/donald-trump-says-i-know-who-my-running-mate-is-2024-polls-at-iowa-townhall-18768841.htm","https://t.co/1jm1U9M99h","https://t.co/ioi6jyQDe7","https://t.co/JUqIRJFxtd","https://twitter.com/RonDeSantis/status/1744433288368804324?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw","https://twitter.com/NikkiHaley/status/1745295026467287432?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw","https://twitter.com/RonDeSantis/status/1745288678706917405?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw","https://t.co/E9T7ylDb2U","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/donald-trump-disqualified-from-2024-ballot-in-colorado-court-says-18606401.htm"],"labels":[],"matchedAuthors":[{"id":"1da1f1686906438f85e594d91ae46e72","name":"Vijay Anand"}],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[{"name":"Donald Trump","weight":0.0767},{"name":"Republican delegates","weight":0.0748},{"name":"Trump","weight":0.0707},{"name":"Florida Governor Ron DeSantis","weight":0.0668},{"name":"July","weight":0.0661},{"name":"delegates","weight":0.0624},{"name":"GOP hopefuls Nikki Haley","weight":0.0616},{"name":"US Presidential Election","weight":0.0595},{"name":"anti-Trump factions","weight":0.059},{"name":"Nikki Haley","weight":0.0588}],"topics":[{"name":"2024 Elections"}],"categories":[{"name":"World"},{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[{"data":"US Presidential Election 2024","type":"EVENT","mentions":2},{"data":"Republican","type":"NORP","mentions":4},{"data":"Iowa","type":"GPE","mentions":4},{"data":"Florida","type":"GPE","mentions":2},{"data":"US","type":"GPE","mentions":2},{"data":"Colorado","type":"GPE","mentions":3},{"data":"Maine","type":"GPE","mentions":3},{"data":"the United States","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"New Jersey","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"South Carolina's","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Ukraine","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Israel","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"GOP","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"the Republican National Convention","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"RNC","type":"ORG","mentions":2},{"data":"Nikki Haley","type":"PERSON","mentions":9},{"data":"Ron DeSantis","type":"PERSON","mentions":8},{"data":"Donald Trump","type":"PERSON","mentions":11},{"data":"Chris Christie","type":"PERSON","mentions":1}],"companies":[],"summary":"The fifth debate between Republican presidential candidates Nikki Haley and Florida Governor Ron DeSantis took place, with both accusing each other of lying and attacking their records and characters. Despite this, Donald Trump remains the leading contender to win the party's nomination at the Republican National Convention (RNC) in July. Despite being barred from appearing on the primary ballots in Colorado and Maine due to lawsuits and formal complaints to election officials in at least 19 other states pending, this makes Trump's path to becoming the Republican nominee that much harder. The estimated number of Republican delegates stands at 2,469, with at least 1,235 delegates needed for a candidate to secure the nomination. If more states like Colorado or Maine overturn these decisions, it will significantly impact Trump's prospects.","translation":"","translatedTitle":"","translatedDescription":"","translatedSummary":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"92fa1da649fa49fba7d68026dcdb43d7","places":[],"people":[{"wikidataId":"Q11668","name":"Nikki Haley"},{"wikidataId":"Q22686","name":"Donald Trump"},{"wikidataId":"Q63879","name":"Chris Christie"},{"wikidataId":"Q3105215","name":"Ron DeSantis"}],"sentiment":{"positive":0.0506,"negative":0.6844,"neutral":0.265}},{"url":"https://irshadgul.com/us-presidential-election-2024-donald-trump-us-presidential-election-2024-joe-biden-vs-trump-they-will-file-a-criminal-case-against-trump-the-court-said-the-law-is-the-same-for-everyone-many/","authorsByline":"","articleId":"19f16e7242c44271a2ee8e0a67d0c9e5","clusterId":"8fa64bd81b5d4501abd6f67f35029741","source":{"domain":"irshadgul.com"},"imageUrl":"https://images.bhaskarassets.com/web2images/521/2024/02/06/2_1707235452.jpg","country":"us","language":"en","pubDate":"2024-02-07T06:35:33+00:00","addDate":"2024-02-07T06:44:22.305030+00:00","refreshDate":"2024-02-07T06:44:22.305031+00:00","score":142.1256,"title":"US Presidential Election 2024","description":"US Presidential Election 2024","content":"Trump’s argument is that he was president in 2020 and cannot be prosecuted under the Constitution for any matter related to that period. (folder)\n\nA US court has ordered criminal proceedings against f... [966 symbols]","medium":"Article","links":[],"labels":[],"matchedAuthors":[],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[{"name":"former President Donald Trump","weight":0.1247},{"name":"Donald Trump","weight":0.1108},{"name":"Tuesday","weight":0.1065},{"name":"Trump","weight":0.0922},{"name":"criminal proceedings","weight":0.0866},{"name":"a federal appeals court","weight":0.0805},{"name":"incumbent Joe Biden","weight":0.0767},{"name":"many options","weight":0.0767},{"name":"Joe Biden","weight":0.0714},{"name":"more news","weight":0.0667}],"topics":[{"name":"2024 Elections"}],"categories":[{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[{"data":"US Presidential Election 2024","type":"EVENT","mentions":1},{"data":"Trump","type":"PERSON","mentions":7},{"data":"Joe Biden","type":"PERSON","mentions":1},{"data":"Constitution","type":"LAW","mentions":1},{"data":"US","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"the ‘New York Times’","type":"ORG","mentions":2},{"data":"the Supreme Court","type":"ORG","mentions":1}],"companies":[],"summary":"A US court has ordered criminal proceedings against former President Donald Trump for allegedly conspiring to overturn the results of the 2020 election. Trump argues that he was president in 2020 and therefore cannot be prosecuted under the Constitution for any matter related to that period. This decision is preliminary, but still leaves many options, including the Supreme Court. This is the first time dealing with such a case.","translation":"","translatedTitle":"","translatedDescription":"","translatedSummary":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"207a63e2580b4e55a53332c90dd33825","places":[],"people":[{"wikidataId":"Q6279","name":"Joe Biden"},{"wikidataId":"Q22686","name":"Donald Trump"}],"sentiment":{"positive":0.0418,"negative":0.781,"neutral":0.1772}},{"url":"https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/us-presidential-election-2024-biden-seriously-considering-dropping-out-report-19437783.htm","authorsByline":"Vijay Anand","articleId":"1b5c5f9bde8c46c2a32df22bda2a73ea","clusterId":"324956ee0e1d4dab9f03e6759929cb87","source":{"domain":"cnbctv18.com"},"imageUrl":"https://images.cnbctv18.com/uploads/2024/07/joe-biden-2024-07-8c17b020ea0b094b4675879da2f8a7ad.jpg?im=FitAndFill,width=500,height=300","country":"in","language":"en","pubDate":"2024-07-03T15:15:15+00:00","addDate":"2024-07-03T15:34:13.334244+00:00","refreshDate":"2024-07-03T15:34:13.334248+00:00","score":142.1256,"title":"US Presidential Election 2024","description":"According to a New York Times report, US President Joe Biden has privately told an ally he is seriously considering whether he can salvage his re-election campaign after a \"devastating\" debate performance. Biden faces an uphill battle to convince voters the debate was an anomaly.","content":"US President Joe Biden has privately told a key ally that he is seriously considering whether he can salvage his bid for re-election after a \"devastating\" performance in last week's presidential debat... [1976 symbols]","medium":"Article","links":["https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/these-are-our-candidates-how-social-media-reacted-to-first-biden-trump-debate-19435108.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/2024-us-presidential-result-biden-vs-trump-how-markets-could-react-19437600.htm","https://www.cnbctv18.com/world/us%c2%ac-presidential-debate-donald-trump-joe-biden-democrats-election-campaign-19435505.htm"],"labels":[],"matchedAuthors":[{"id":"1da1f1686906438f85e594d91ae46e72","name":"Vijay Anand"}],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[{"name":"US President Joe Biden","weight":0.0996},{"name":"Joe Biden","weight":0.0979},{"name":"Biden","weight":0.097},{"name":"former President Donald Trump","weight":0.0737},{"name":"White House officials","weight":0.0721},{"name":"NYT","weight":0.0695},{"name":"US Presidential Election","weight":0.0692},{"name":"White House","weight":0.0691},{"name":"campaign stops","weight":0.0677},{"name":"key battleground states","weight":0.0647}],"topics":[{"name":"2024 Elections"}],"categories":[{"name":"World"},{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[{"data":"US","type":"GPE","mentions":3},{"data":"Atlanta","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Pennsylvania","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Wisconsin","type":"GPE","mentions":1},{"data":"Joe Biden","type":"PERSON","mentions":8},{"data":"Donald Trump","type":"PERSON","mentions":2},{"data":"The New York Times","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"NYT","type":"ORG","mentions":4},{"data":"CBS News","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"Fivethirtyeight.com","type":"ORG","mentions":1},{"data":"White House","type":"ORG","mentions":2}],"companies":[],"summary":"US President Joe Biden is considering his re-election bid after a \"devastating\" performance in the presidential debate, according to a report in The New York Times. This is the first public indication that Biden is weighing whether to continue his campaign. The report also highlighted concerns about his viability as a candidate following his \"halting and unfocused\" debate appearance. Despite these concerns, Biden's allies maintain that he remains in the fight and sees the situation as an opportunity to stage a comeback. As a result, he is currently polling at 40.2%, 1.6 points behind Republican leader Donald Trump.","translation":"","translatedTitle":"","translatedDescription":"","translatedSummary":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"99d9f40668b646bcbb36a453403585b1","places":[],"people":[{"wikidataId":"Q6279","name":"Joe Biden"},{"wikidataId":"Q22686","name":"Donald Trump"}],"sentiment":{"positive":0.096,"negative":0.6076,"neutral":0.2964}},{"url":"https://actualnewsmagazine.com/english/us-presidential-election-automated-accounts-fuel-disinformation-about-x/","authorsByline":"Anuj CHOPRA","articleId":"c6ba6fff060142f1ad39551fe082ee2b","clusterId":"790ecdf964b049b3bccf866d302e7a65","source":{"domain":"actualnewsmagazine.com"},"imageUrl":"https://actualnewsmagazine.com/english/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/US-Presidential-Election-Automated-Accounts-Fuel-Disinformation-About-X.jpg","country":"us","language":"en","pubDate":"2024-07-31T22:56:48+00:00","addDate":"2024-07-31T23:26:09.040913+00:00","refreshDate":"2024-07-31T23:26:09.040915+00:00","score":142.1256,"title":"2024 - US Presidential Election","description":"(Washington) Automated accounts on X that spread disinformation and hate speech ahead of the British election are now amplifying conspiracy theories","content":"","medium":"Article","links":[],"labels":[{"name":"Low Content"}],"matchedAuthors":[{"id":"f0b5118b85a8453eab9d5e15dcd7fc46","name":"Anuj Chopra"}],"claim":"","verdict":"","keywords":[],"topics":[{"name":"Media"}],"categories":[{"name":"Politics"}],"entities":[],"companies":[],"summary":"","translation":"","translatedTitle":"","translatedDescription":"","translatedSummary":"","locations":[],"reprint":false,"reprintGroupId":"42449e6df368460e8f3bb5c72232cf16","places":[],"people":[],"sentiment":{}}]
